Long John Nebel Papers
Long John Nebel Papers
- Tapes
  - Miscellaneous
    - "Wacka Ding Hoy" (Record) Bill Wilson, Lee Jones, Larry Wagner, undated; nebel_1813; 1 reel (1/4"x600') (Oversize 90)
    - Joe Cassidy (not played), undated; nebel_1815; 1 reel (Oversize 90)
    - "Malcolm Boyd Easter Show", undated; nebel_1816; 1 reel (Oversize 90)